BULLET PUNCH  |  MANTIS SHRIMP
THE MANTIS SHRIMP IS
A TRUE HEAVY HITTER.
TAKE THIS ONE. SHE'S
ABOUT TO DEVOUR THIS
SNAIL, BUT SHE'S GOT
TO CRACK IT OPEN
FIRST, SO SHE CAREFULLY
POSITIONS IT. THEN… DAMN!
SHE PUNCHES IT WITH
THE SPEED OF A
22 -HOLLIVER BULLET. IT'S
THE FASTEST ATTACK IN
THE ANIMAL KINGDOM. THAT'S
ONE KIND OF MANTIS
SHRIMP, KNOWN AS A
SMASHER. HERE'S THE OTHER.
THIS ONE'S CALLED A
SPIRROR. BURIED UP TO
HIS EYEBALLS, HE WATCHES
AND WAITS. THEN… HE'S
PREY ON A SERRATED
BLADE WITH BLINDING SPEED
AND DRAGGING IT BENEATH
THE SAND. WHAT MAKES
THESE TWO SO AMAZING
ISN'T JUST THEIR SPEED.
IT'S THEIR EYES. SEE
THOSE BLACK SPOTS? THEY'RE
LIKE OUR PUPILS, WHERE
THE LIGHT ENTERS THE
EYE. WE HUMANS HAVE
ONE IN EACH EYE.
EACH SENDS AN IMAGE
TO THE BRAIN AND
VOILA! DEPTH PERCEPTION. THE
MANTIS SHRIMP HAS SIX
OF THEM. OUR VISION,
BINOCULAR. HIS VISION, HEX
-NOCULAR. FOR WHEN ACCURACY
COUNTS.